<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HnM</string>
    <string name="bmi2">::Health and Vitality Diet Plan

        Breakfast Diet Plan Balance with Red Fruit cereal, a glass of fruit smoothie and a yogurt
Lunch
Chicken tikka breast slices with coriander on multi-seeded bread with a fruity cereal bar and satsuma
Dinner
Fresh haddock fish cakes with new potatoes and a tomato salad with dressing. A glass of white wine.
Snacks
Crispbread snack with soft cheese topping and a bowl of fresh strawberries</string>
    <string name="bmi3">
::Feel fuller diet plan
breakfast
Beans on toast with a glass of milk and bowl of fresh strawberries
lunch
Smoked salmon, soft cheese and watercress filled bagel with yogurt and nectarine
dinner
Salmon fillet in watercress sauce with new potatoes, asparagus spears and carrots. Yogurt biscuit dessert
snacks
Half a galia melon and toffee coated popcorn snack
</string>
    <string name="bmi4">::VEGETARIAN DIET PLAN
BREAKFAST
Diet Plan raisin wheats breakfast cereal, a glass of grapefruit juice and satsuma
LUNCH
Fresh carrot and coriander soup with multi-seeded bread, half a melon and yogurt
SNACKS
Vegetable stuffed spuds with a watercress and tomato salad and dressing. A yogurt dessert plus a bunch of seedless grapes
DINNER
Crispbread snack with low fat spread and seedless grapes plus a handful of whole almonds</string>


    <string name="bmi1">
::REDUCED FAT DIET PLAN
BREAKFAST
Diet Plan raisin wheats breakfast cereal with banana chips and  fresh raspberries
LUNCH
Turkey and tomato salad wholemeal sandwich with a chocolate mousse and piece of fruit
SNACKS
Italian Meatball bolognese with wholewheat pasta and a piece of fruit for dessert
DINNER
Wholemeal Toast, Yogurt, Strawberries
</string>


    <string-array name="nearby_gyms">
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>
        <item> GYM A</item>

    </string-array>




    <string name="ustrasan">Benefits of Camel Pose:
Reduces fat on thighs.
Opens up the hips, stretching deep hip flexors.
Stretches and strengthens the shoulders and back.
Expands the abdominal region, improving digestion and elimination.
</string>

    <string name="chakrasan">
        Benefits of snake pose:
Strengthens your spine
Stimulates abdominal organs
Reduces belly fat
Manage stress
Improves circulation
</string>
    <string name="bhujangaasan">
      Benefits of Chakrasana:
Strengthens liver, pancreas and kidneys.
Excellent for heart.
Good for infertility, asthma and osteoporosis.
Strengthens arms, shoulders, hands, wrists and legs.
Stretches the chest and lungs.
Strengthens the arms and wrists, legs.
</string>
     <string name="suryanamaskar">
      benefits of sn:
Helps lose weight
Helps strengthen muscles and joints
Gives glowing skin
Ensures a better functioning digestive system
</string>

</resources>
